<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<errors>
	
	<!-- MySQL -->
	<error code="500" reason="mysql_connection_failed">
		<msg>MySQL Database Connection failed.</msg>
		<doc>Make sure the MySQL service has been started. Make sure the required database exists and the connection information is correct. This is configured
		inside app/config/mysql.php. The connection is initiated inside config\resources\clients\[client].php and handled
		inside the Application class in app\classes\application.php. A firewall may also be preventing you from connecting 
		if you are not connecting to localhost, in which case you'll need to whitelist your IP in the target server firewall's configuration.
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<!-- Routes and views -->
	<error code="404" reason="route_not_found">
		<msg>Resource not found.</msg>
		<doc>If the page was not found it probably means the route does not exist. 
		Make sure the request has a compatible route setup inside app\routes\[client]\index.php.
		This whitelists the request and points it to a specific handler, which allows you to load a specific
		module, frame file, template, and setup your own custom variables depending on the request.
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<error code="500" reason="view_not_found">
		<msg>Required resource not found.</msg>
		<doc>The route exists but the view does not. You must create the appropriate view file inside
		app\views\[context]\[client]\[module].php, where "module" is what was specified within the route.
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<error code="500" reason="shared_view_not_found">
		<msg>Required resource not found.</msg>
		<doc>The route exists but the shared view does not. The shared view is required for rendering a view. 
		You must create the appropriate shared view file inside 
		app\views\shared\[client]\[frame].php, where "frame" is what was specified within the main route view (index.php).
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<!-- Resources -->
	
	<error code="403" reason="resource_invalid_token">
		<msg>Forbidden.</msg>
		<doc>The token for this request has expired. A new CSRF token should be generated for every form. 
			The token gets placed into the view and gets interpreted by the Resource client. It is created based on the resource request. 
			You will need to analyse why the tokens might be different. Perhaps the resource path supplied in the form
			is different from the request. See app\views\shared\resource\index.php for the file that handles the Resource requests. 
			If you are making AJAX requests, the token should not be expiring at all, since a new token cannot ordinarly 
			be generated by an AJAX interface (it must happen on page reload).
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<error code="422" reason="task_resource_mismatch">
		<msg>Bad syntax.</msg>
		<doc>The task does not match the resource provided. You should not provide a resource Id when making a request to create a new resource. 
		Check the resource path and task - they may be configured incorrectly.
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<error code="422" reason="resource_data_handler_error">
		<msg>Incomplete or incorrect request.</msg>
		<doc>The request could not complete because of an data handler error. This is probably due to user inputted information, for example, if they entered 
		an email address in the incorrect format, or the email address already exists. 
		</doc>
	</error>
	
	<!-- Users -->
	<error code="403" reason="user_login_required">
		<msg>Forbidden.</msg>
		<doc>The user is required to login. If the user should be logged in at this point, a session conflict of some kind may be occurring.	
		</doc>
	</error>
	
</errors>
